I know y'all be forgetting I'm bad as hell.
I know, I know.
But I just want to remind you, I cleans up nice.
I do.
And I will be in San Diego tonight with my Truth Translator Sound Sessions Tour.
You can catch me in Harlem on Wednesday.
You can catch me in Baltimore on Thursday.
And I'm hoping to see you there.
Harlem, we're going to be at Comedy in Harlem.
And in Baltimore, we're going to be at the Dark Room in Baltimore.
And you know, more importantly, we're going to be listening to Truth Translator when it drops on Sunday.
That's what we're going to be doing.
I'm back in my music bag and Amanda Diva 2.0 is loading.
My new album, Truth Translator, drops June 14th.
Head to AmandaDivaMusic.com to hear the album, to support the work through merch,
and to find out when I'm going to be in your city with a free sound session.
This ain't a movement, it's movement music.